<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Christopher McKenzie</title>
    <link>https://chrismckenzie.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Christopher McKenzie</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://chrismckenzie.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A little tuneup</title>
      <link>https://chrismckenzie.io/projects/k5/posts/a-little-tuneup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrismckenzie.io/projects/k5/posts/a-little-tuneup/</guid>
      <description>Mind the grease, this k5 came to me with a 350ci small block chevy (sbc) from an mid 80s passenger car from what I can gather. looking at the vin this k5 was originally equipped with a 400ci sbc (bit of a bummer that isn&amp;rsquo;t still in it) but this engine runs decent and will remain there until I can figure out what to put in it.
In the mean time this engine needed a small tuneup, namely in the ignition category at first the engine has a slight miss which I determined was just a fouled plug due to the electric choke not being hooked up and being flooded on start replaced the plugs and that resolved that but the I wanted to see where the timing was so I put a timing light on it and found that the advance mechanism was not working, I quickly jumped on Jegs and found an entire kit for a replacement distributor for very reasonable, it even came with plug wires.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying Anything with Dropship</title>
      <link>https://chrismckenzie.io/posts/deploy-anything/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrismckenzie.io/posts/deploy-anything/</guid>
      <description>So it has been a while since I last touched on the problem of deploying software to a server, with that being said I have had a chance to really dig in and find a solution that is flexible as well as simple for developers to setup.
The Idea So when I started down this path of finding a clean deployment flow for my company (The Control Group) I had a few requirements It had to work for all of the different types of applications and languages that we build; I also did not want to use web hooks they are just too clunky and you have to have a server that is accesible on the internet so it can be called (not really a fan); The last thing that I wanted to be able to do is to deploy multiple versions of an application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breakfast Burrito</title>
      <link>https://chrismckenzie.io/recipes/breakfast_burrito/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2015 23:16:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrismckenzie.io/recipes/breakfast_burrito/</guid>
      <description> This recipe serves 8
Ingredients  2 lb - Tillamook Medium Cheddar Cheese 1 lb - Sage Sausage 2 lb - Thick cut peppered bacon 16 - Eggs 1 tbsp - Butter 8 - XXL Flour Tortillas  Instructions  Cook Sausage, Bacon, and Eggs seperately Mix All Ingredients in pot with cheese Wrap ~1lb of mixture in lightly warmed tortilla.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spaghetti</title>
      <link>https://chrismckenzie.io/recipes/spaghetti/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2015 23:12:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrismckenzie.io/recipes/spaghetti/</guid>
      <description> Ingredients  1 - 106oz. Can Tomato Sauce 8- 6oz. Can Tomato Paste 1&amp;frasl;2 Cup Granulated Garlic 1&amp;frasl;3 Cup Whole Oregano 3&amp;frasl;8 Cup Worcestershire 1&amp;frasl;3 Cup Italian Dressing 1&amp;frasl;8 Cup Lemon Juice 1&amp;frasl;8 Cup Sugar 2 Pounds Hamburger (pre-cooked) 3- 4oz. Can Mushrooms (Optional) 1 1&amp;frasl;2 Cans of Water (Tomato Sauce Can) dash of pepper  Instructions  In large pot place first 8 ingredients than add 1&amp;frasl;2 Can of water and mix thoroughly (can us mixer if needed) Once thoroughly mixed add rest of water and stir by hand Heat on low flame until hot throughout stirring occasionally Turn off stove and let mixture cool Turn on stove low flame again and again heat sauce Brown meat in skillet until thoroughly cooked Drain all fat off of meat and rinse thoroughly Add meat to sauce May add mushrooms if desired Heat and cool approximately 6 hours serve with evergood hot links  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying with Go</title>
      <link>https://chrismckenzie.io/posts/deploying-with-golang/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrismckenzie.io/posts/deploying-with-golang/</guid>
      <description>Recently I have been building a lot of go applications, and I think I have come up with a good pattern for building an app that is ready for deployment to either a server or to users. This includes build/run for development, testing, dependency management, and packaging. While this process is still being actively developed I believe it is at a state in which to share.
The Structure I keep a very simple structure for my projects and it is as follows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accord</title>
      <link>https://chrismckenzie.io/projects/accord/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrismckenzie.io/projects/accord/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bowen Masco</title>
      <link>https://chrismckenzie.io/colleagues/bowen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrismckenzie.io/colleagues/bowen/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dropship</title>
      <link>https://chrismckenzie.io/projects/dropship/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrismckenzie.io/projects/dropship/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joel Guerra</title>
      <link>https://chrismckenzie.io/colleagues/joel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrismckenzie.io/colleagues/joel/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preflight</title>
      <link>https://chrismckenzie.io/projects/preflight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrismckenzie.io/projects/preflight/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Varun Kumar</title>
      <link>https://chrismckenzie.io/colleagues/varun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrismckenzie.io/colleagues/varun/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>